Marijn van der Zee

- ₾ Dolf
- marijn@serraict.com
- +31(0)6 387 414 82
- http://www.serraict.com

SUMMARY

I love to guide software teams on their journey to deliver valuable software and becoming a great team.

I am a Scrum Master/Agile Coach, agile developer, pragmatic student, team player and coach and have been active in the field of software development for well over ten years.

SKILLS

- Software Development
- Process Improvement

• Scrum

Coaching

• C#

• .NET

EXPERIENCE

TransFollow BV

01 / 2016 - Present

Agile Coach (independent contractor)

Guiding the Scrum Master, Product Owner, two agile teams and the organisation on their journey to deliver the TransFollow platform for exchanging consignment information.

Serra ICT Diensten

11 / 2009 - Present

Owner

Serra helps organizations to grow great software teams that reliably deliver valuable software.

Logiqs B.V.

01 / 2011 - Present

Consultant (independent contractor)

TransFollow BV

01 / 2015 - 12 / 2015

Scrum Master TransFollow (independent contractor)

Ensuring that Scrum is understood and enacted by the Scrum Team and the TransFollow organisation.

Beurtvaartadres BV

04 / 2014 - 01 / 2015

Design Team Lead (ad interim)

Coordinating activities for the design team working on the TransFollow project. www.transfollow.com/ - the standardised digital consignment note.

Nitea IT Solutions

08 / 2010 - 06 / 2012

Consultant (independent contractor)

Developing software and coaching the development team.

Olsthoorn Automatisering

03 / 2010 - 12 / 2011

Software Engineer (independent contractor)

Developing some small applications, mainly for the web.

Nitea 01 / 2010 - 07 / 2010

Software Architect (independent contractor)

Designing an architecture for a labor registration application to be used in greenhouse horticulture. Advising the development team during inception, elaboration and construction phases.

Logiqs B.V. 09 / 2005 - 09 / 2009

Systems Analist and Software Architect

Technical lead for the application suite Dat-A-Control, a set of applications for controlling various production and logistic processes in automated pot plant nurseries; best compared to MES/WMS systems known from other industries. Project management.

Quel.nl 2001 - 2004

Web Developer

Part-time web developer.

EDUCATION Delft University

Delft University of Technology

1998 - 2005

MSc , Mechanical Engineering, specialization Transportation Engineering and Logistics

DSBV Punch (Basketball); Dispuut Transportkunde

Praedinius Gymnasium Groningen

1992 - 1998

VWO

Nederlandse Basketball Bond

2012 - 2013

02 / 2016

Basketball Trainer 4

CERTIFICATIONS

rofessional	l Scrum Practicioner	
-------------	----------------------	--

Scrum.org · License: PSP, 121566

Professional Scrum Master I 12 / 2014

Scrum.org · License: PSM I, 121566

Basketball Trainer 4 05 / 2013

NBB (Nederlanse Basketball Bond)

Professional Scrum Developer I 09 / 2015

Scrum.org · License: PSD I, 121566

Professional Scrum Product Owner I 08 / 2015

Scrum.org · License: PSPO I, 121566

Applying the ANSI/ISA-95 standard 12 / 2010

ISA

Implementing business to MES integration using the ANSI/ISA-95 standards 12 / 2011

ISA Europe

Praktisch Leidinggeven 2006

NCOI

Customizing Your Team Workflow with the Best of Kanban and Scrum 06 / 2015

LANGUAGES

• Dutch (NATIVE_OR_BILINGUAL)

• English (PROFESSIONAL_WORKING)

PUBLICATIONS

Dynamic Free Range Routing for Automated Guided Vehicles

08 / 2006

Proceedings of the 2006 IEEE International Conference on Networking, Sensing and Control, 2006. ICNSC '06.

· Authors: Marijn van der Zee, M.B. Duinkerken, G. Lodewijks ·

http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/search/freesrchabstract.jsp?tp=&arnumber=1673164

In this paper an algorithm is presented that allows for dynamic free range route planning for automated guided vehicles (AGVs). This routing algorithm is based on the route choice methodology from a microscopic pedestrian behavioral model. Until now, AGVs use a map of predefined, fixed paths that are combined to obtain routes along which they move from origin to destination point. Although it allows for reliable and safe automation of vehicles with limited maneuverability, the use of fixed paths leads to unnecessary long routes, congestion, deadlocks and makes the routing system vulnerable to disruptions at the level of route execution. The developed routing algorithm dynamically determines free ranging trajectories that are optimized regarding arrival time while avoiding static obstacles and collisions with other AGVs.

Blog 10 / 2015

Serra ICT · Authors: Marijn van der Zee · $\underline{\text{http://www.serraict.com/blog}}$

My blog, mainly on Agile Software Development.